<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Devon Walshe</title>
    <link>https://devonwalshe.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Devon Walshe</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 15:58:02 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://devonwalshe.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Rugiet Health</title>
      <link>https://devonwalshe.github.io/portfolio/rugiet/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 15:58:02 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devonwalshe.github.io/portfolio/rugiet/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lsaquo; &amp;rsaquo; About Link to heading Rugiet is a direct to consumer healthcare company based in Austin, TX, disrupting the traditional compounding pharmaceutical industry with a mix of telehealth and customised healthcare provision. I joined the company in the summer of 2020 with a remit to pay down the significant technical debt that the company had accumulated during its get-to-market phase, and bring some order to the software development practices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Treasury Pay</title>
      <link>https://devonwalshe.github.io/portfolio/treasurypay/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devonwalshe.github.io/portfolio/treasurypay/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lsaquo; &amp;rsaquo; About Link to heading In 2018 I was transitionint to full time remote work - and my fist significant contract project was a financial platform for global retailers with Invictus Gurus, a consultancy based in Dallas, Tx.
The software manages high throughput point-of-sale transactions and offers companies with a global retail footprint the opportunity to get highly granular metrics on their banking, revenue and forecasting data.
I was initially engaged to bring the proof of concept application back online after some unexpected downtime.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transforming Glasgow</title>
      <link>https://devonwalshe.github.io/portfolio/transforming-glasgow/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devonwalshe.github.io/portfolio/transforming-glasgow/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lsaquo; &amp;rsaquo; About Link to heading At the end of the 2 year Future Cities programme - which functioned independently from the city government - I was brought in-house to work on the council&amp;rsquo;s $250m transformation programme. I was remanded to the team tasked with finding data-led solutionst to financial and organisational challenges.
My previous role had set me up well - with a good network of the data stakeholders and knowledge of how to work with and around the beaurocratic challenges that come along with a large political institution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Future Cities</title>
      <link>https://devonwalshe.github.io/portfolio/future-cities/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devonwalshe.github.io/portfolio/future-cities/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lsaquo; &amp;rsaquo; About Link to heading In 2015 I was approached to apply for a role at Future Cities Glasgow - a large infrastructure and innovation programme kicking off at the city of Glasgow.
Through my work with Sync I’d become active in the open data &amp;amp; hackathon communities and I was brought on to Future Cities to lead an open data initiative - Open Glasgow - and produce a series of high profile Hackathons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Demarco Digital Archive</title>
      <link>https://devonwalshe.github.io/portfolio/demarco/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devonwalshe.github.io/portfolio/demarco/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lsaquo; &amp;rsaquo; About Link to heading Richard Demarco is cultural institution in Scotland - notable for his prolific photography work documenting an alternative arts history from the 1970’s to present day, inviting internationally renowned artists to Scotland and developing an international art community in his home country.
The university of Dundee had at significant effort over several years digitised his archive but attempts to bring it online had run into some issues - so they approached me to take on the project of redeveloping the site and making the archive more accessible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sync</title>
      <link>https://devonwalshe.github.io/portfolio/sync/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 1969 18:33:32 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devonwalshe.github.io/portfolio/sync/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lsaquo; &amp;rsaquo; About Link to heading Sync was 2 year government funded research &amp;amp; prototyping programme bringing together technology and the creative sector, with the aim to set up a policy roadmap for industry and governement.
I was graciously invited to join as a result of my work in the developer &amp;amp; data communities, and worked alongside an extremely talented individuals from technology, design and production backgrounds. Sync was like a small strategic superhero group for technology and the creative sector.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TechCube</title>
      <link>https://devonwalshe.github.io/portfolio/techcube/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 1969 18:33:32 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devonwalshe.github.io/portfolio/techcube/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lsaquo; &amp;rsaquo; About Link to heading Another example of my entrepreneurial instincts getting the better of me, I found myself co-founding a community-led project to renovate an old 7 floor university tower into Scotland’s first privately funded technology incubator.
Started like all things of the nature - a casual conversation at the local tech-meetup turns into a speculative text to the owner of the building, which turns into a &amp;lsquo;yes&amp;rsquo; and us getting our hands on a decommissioned lab tower in central Edinburgh.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Festivals Review</title>
      <link>https://devonwalshe.github.io/portfolio/festivals-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 1969 18:33:31 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devonwalshe.github.io/portfolio/festivals-review/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lsaquo; &amp;rsaquo; About Link to heading Edinburgh hosts the world’s largest art’s festival every year in August - actually a conglomeration of 10+ individually organised festivals.
There are hundreds of things to see every day and picking the good ones is notoriously difficult - so a small cottage industry of publications pops up every year, but the quality of content and reliability is just as variable as the shows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Journal</title>
      <link>https://devonwalshe.github.io/portfolio/the-journal/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 1969 18:33:27 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devonwalshe.github.io/portfolio/the-journal/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lsaquo; &amp;rsaquo; About Link to heading The Journal was our youthful, rebellious take on where hard hitting news media needed to go. It was a time of significant transition in journalism, as publishers found their feet online - competing against sensationalist blogs and farmed content.
I had become heavily involved in journalism in my first years at university - including a run as editor of the historic Student newspaper, and with a team of talented writers and editors, we decided to launch our own independent journalism platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photography</title>
      <link>https://devonwalshe.github.io/portfolio/photography/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 1969 18:33:25 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devonwalshe.github.io/portfolio/photography/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lsaquo; &amp;rsaquo; About Link to heading The passion for photography that I developed during my travelling days continued at university as I started experimenting with film and different genres - specifically journalism, fashion and architectural photography. I love taking pictures because they represent a moment in time, from a particular angle or perspective. For me good photography make you look twice at something ordinary, or help you see something that wasn&amp;rsquo;t immediately obvious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drifter</title>
      <link>https://devonwalshe.github.io/portfolio/drifter/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 1969 18:33:24 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devonwalshe.github.io/portfolio/drifter/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lsaquo; &amp;rsaquo; About Link to heading A long time ago, when blogs were still called weblogs, I built a journaling website to document my early nomadic period - as a 19 year old setting off on a 2 year long adventure taking me around the world without flying.
Over the course of this period I posted some outragiously cringy travel writing, the musings of an angsty late teenager trying to make sense of the world as I saw it passing by on sail-boats, trains and buses.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
