<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Selected Portfolio on Devon Walshe</title>
    <link>https://devonwalshe.github.io/portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Selected Portfolio on Devon Walshe</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 13:48:19 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://devonwalshe.github.io/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Journal</title>
      <link>https://devonwalshe.github.io/portfolio/the-journal/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 1969 18:33:27 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devonwalshe.github.io/portfolio/the-journal/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lsaquo; &amp;rsaquo; About Link to heading The Journal was our youthful, rebellious take on where hard hitting news media needed to go. It was a time of significant transition in journalism, as publishers found their feet online - competing against sensationalist blogs and farmed content.
I had become heavily involved in journalism in my first years at university - including a run as editor of the historic Student newspaper, and with a team of talented writers and editors, we decided to launch our own independent journalism platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photography</title>
      <link>https://devonwalshe.github.io/portfolio/photography/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 1969 18:33:25 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devonwalshe.github.io/portfolio/photography/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lsaquo; &amp;rsaquo; About Link to heading The passion for photography that I developed during my travelling days continued at university as I started experimenting with film and different genres - specifically journalism, fashion and architectural photography. I love taking pictures because they represent a moment in time, from a particular angle or perspective. For me good photography make you look twice at something ordinary, or help you see something that wasn&amp;rsquo;t immediately obvious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drifter</title>
      <link>https://devonwalshe.github.io/portfolio/drifter/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 1969 18:33:24 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devonwalshe.github.io/portfolio/drifter/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lsaquo; &amp;rsaquo; About Link to heading A long time ago, when blogs were still called weblogs, I built a journaling website to document my early nomadic period - as a 19 year old setting off on a 2 year long adventure taking me around the world without flying.
Over the course of this period I posted some outragiously cringy travel writing, the musings of an angsty late teenager trying to make sense of the world as I saw it passing by on sail-boats, trains and buses.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
